<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[FluentGuitar]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[FluentGuitar]]></description>
        <link>http://fluentguitar.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 20:29:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://fluentguitar.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Me]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Me</h1><p>Justin Martinez is classically trained guitarist who 
has been performing at special events for over 10 years. His guitar 
music adds an elegant touch to any occasion. From classical to 
contemporary, Justin’s music enhances the ambiance during all types of 
events, including wedding ceremonies, cocktail hours, rehearsal dinners,
 private parties, wine tastings, corporate events, and community 
festivals. He is dedicated to providing the perfect flavor for each 
occasion and tailors all music selections to express the theme of the 
event.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fluentguitar.com/about-me/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb28845-0bfb-4010-9ae4-71cb171e1962</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 20:51:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lessons]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Lessons</h1><p>One-on-one lessons are a great way to start diving in and taking on music in depth. However, I believe the best way to learn and practice what you learn in a lesson is to play with other musicians. This is where most lessons stop short and where most musicians get hung up. Nothing can replace the learn-by-doing approach of playing with other music, and the sheer joy that is communicating with another human being with music. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3026e7efa0950fa3d2d77b50472429ae3399118c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fluentguitar.com/lessons/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b3e8f9a8-c208-43a8-b2fe-b97dd2e8be42</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 20:45:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Your Own Unique, Original Wedding Music!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Your Own Unique, Original Wedding Music!</h1><p>Looking to make your wedding day even more special and unique? Tired of hearing "Here Comes the Bride" or "Pachelbell's Canon" at every wedding you have ever been to? Why not have your own original wedding music? Part of hiring a live musician to play during the ceremony is having the flexibility to play different styles and custom tailor the music to fit your personalities. I have performed hundreds of wedding ceremonies and have worked with all manners of wedding couples to find different musical selections - I know what works. My ability to custom tailor the wedding music doesn't stop at picking the tunes. I also write totally original music! You can have your own unique wedding theme music. Whether it's classical, rock, country, bluegrass, folk, pop or R&B, I can give you your own song. Take a look at the different levels and see what's right for you. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fluentguitar.com/your-own-unique-original-wedding-music/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">19ca21c3-141f-4d38-8847-789f69acc049</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>